### AN CAO

#### JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER

**\** +358 44 989 1921

A Ylioppilaantie 8C 37, 90130 Oulu, Finland

Vietnamese (native) / English

**y** /kcjpop

My main goal as a developer is always to deliver clean, efficient and maintainable code. In order to achieve that, I'm constantly practicing myself, learning about new trends and advancements in the industry, and applying best practices and modern tool-chains into my work-flow. As an experienced JavaScript developer with over 5-year experience, I believe the key to build successful applications is using "the right tool for the right job", not chasing the hype. Currently I find myself interested in functional programming and function languages, and would like to improve my knowledge in that field.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCES**

## **Mobilespot Oy** — Full-stack Developer

May 2016 - March 2018

Mobilespot's main product is <u>Picco</u>, an online photo service for businesses to promote their branch via social networks. Users can use the web app to upload pictures/ take photos using webcam, decorate them with frames/ stickers present the business' image, and share to Facebook or Twitter.

My primary tasks:

- · Built the backend API using PHP on Laravel framework to store photos and interact with third-party services
- Designed and implemented the frontend using MithrilJS, Webpack and HTML5 Canvas
- Deployed and managed the service's server on Linode

# **Haltian Oy** — Contracted Frontend Developer

September 2016 - November 2017

<u>Haltian Oy</u> is an IoT company based in Oulu, Finland. Their services include hardware prototyping, product design, product validation and testing. I participated in a team to build Thingsee operation cloud, a complete IoT solution for businesses, and was responsible for the frontend development.

My primary tasks:

- Used React, Redux, Webpack, D3.js and Tachyons to build the UI for IoT device management and analysis
- Integrated with **Amazon Cognito** to provide authentication and authorization
- Besides, I was also responsible for frontend development of two outsourcing IoT projects for customers from Finland and Israel.

Mypose Oy — Full-stack Developer

November 2014 - May 2016

Mypose Oy's main product is Mypose machines that have a 40-inch touch screen, an integrated full HD camera

and Mypose software. Businesses could use the machines to promote their brand on social media (Facebook,

Twitter, or email) via user-captured pictures, which has frames and stickers expressing business' image.

My primary tasks:

• Designed and built a backend service for Mypose machines to send photos, store them in server and upload

to social networks. Tech stacks: PHP, Laravel, Webpack, MithrilJS, etc.

• Implemented a web app for Mypose's customers to manage their rented devices, view captured photos via

gallery, measure marketing campaign performance.

• For Mypose's staff, provided a web-based tool to manage all devices and customer contracts, configure

devices remotely, view photo gallery and analyze customer campaigns' performance

• Migrated the old Mypose web system into a new server on Linode

varaa.com — Remote Full-stack Developer

**July 2014 - October 2015** 

Varaa.com provided an online solution for customers to make appointments with beauty and cosmetics

businesses in Finland. Later, the company planned to expand to other booking-based sectors such as personal

training, car washing, etc.

My main tasks:

• Migrate the legacy system into Laravel framework

• Developed features using CoffeeScript, MithilJS, etc.

**EDUCATIONS** 

Oulu University of Applied Sciences — Bachelor of Business Information Technology

2012 - 2016 / Oulu, Finland

Thesis: Evaluate and Improve Social Marketing Effectiveness for Customers of Mypose Oy

Grade: 5/5

**HUTECH University of Technology** — Bachelor of Engineering, Software Engineering

2007 - 2011 / Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Thesis: Building a Social Network Using Redis

Grade: 10/10

2